[{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980279203,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":26913,"timeElapsed":93265},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980289250,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":10046,"timeElapsed":103313},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980300394,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":11142,"timeElapsed":114457},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980303386,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":2991,"timeElapsed":117449},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980321122,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":17734,"timeElapsed":135185},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980332554,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":11430,"timeElapsed":146617},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980344842,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":12287,"timeElapsed":158905},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980349250,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":4407,"timeElapsed":163313},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980352234,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"158","question":"Where did you go to high school? What was your high school like?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2982,"timeElapsed":166296},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980366930,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":10782,"timeElapsed":180992},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980371489,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":4558,"timeElapsed":185552},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980374098,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2607,"timeElapsed":188161},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980382217,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":8118,"timeElapsed":196280},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980386977,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":4758,"timeElapsed":201040},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980393833,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6854,"timeElapsed":207896},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980398241,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4407,"timeElapsed":212304},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980403417,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":5175,"timeElapsed":217480},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980410145,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":6727,"timeElapsed":224208},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980421209,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":9079,"timeElapsed":235272},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980424873,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":3663,"timeElapsed":238936},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980427633,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":2759,"timeElapsed":241696},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980430393,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":2759,"timeElapsed":244456},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980433737,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":3343,"timeElapsed":247800},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980436681,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2942,"timeElapsed":250744},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980439562,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2879,"timeElapsed":253625},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980442833,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":3270,"timeElapsed":256896},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980446265,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":3431,"timeElapsed":260328},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980465209,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":17134,"timeElapsed":279272},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980467601,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":2391,"timeElapsed":281664},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980469841,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":2239,"timeElapsed":283904},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980471977,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2135,"timeElapsed":286040},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980474689,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":2710,"timeElapsed":288752},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980477137,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":2447,"timeElapsed":291200},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980479329,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":2191,"timeElapsed":293392},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980482017,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":2687,"timeElapsed":296080},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980484344,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"234","question":"Describe the weather where you are currently. Is this unusual weather for this time of year?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":2326,"timeElapsed":298407},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980499697,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":14351,"timeElapsed":313760},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980502256,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2558,"timeElapsed":316319},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980504993,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2735,"timeElapsed":319056},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980507441,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2447,"timeElapsed":321503},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980509945,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2503,"timeElapsed":324008},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980512384,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2438,"timeElapsed":326447},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980514576,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2191,"timeElapsed":328639},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980516977,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2399,"timeElapsed":331040},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980528841,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":11862,"timeElapsed":342903},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980532193,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":3351,"timeElapsed":346256},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980553296,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":19087,"timeElapsed":367359},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980556408,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":3111,"timeElapsed":370471},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980557905,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":1494,"timeElapsed":371968},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980559912,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":2005,"timeElapsed":373975},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980562632,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":2719,"timeElapsed":376695},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980564520,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":1887,"timeElapsed":378583},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980567496,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":2975,"timeElapsed":381559},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980570272,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":2774,"timeElapsed":384335},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980572664,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":2391,"timeElapsed":386727},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980586592,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":12606,"timeElapsed":400655},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980588488,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":1895,"timeElapsed":402551},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980590600,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":2111,"timeElapsed":404663},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980592744,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":2143,"timeElapsed":406807},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980594880,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":2135,"timeElapsed":408943},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980600128,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":5247,"timeElapsed":414191},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980602680,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2551,"timeElapsed":416743},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980605832,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":3150,"timeElapsed":419895},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980609208,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3375,"timeElapsed":423271},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980622264,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":11958,"timeElapsed":436327},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980624456,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":2191,"timeElapsed":438519},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980626608,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":2151,"timeElapsed":440671},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980629296,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":2687,"timeElapsed":443359},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980636136,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6838,"timeElapsed":450199},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980643792,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":7654,"timeElapsed":457855},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980646912,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":3119,"timeElapsed":460975},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980648728,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":1815,"timeElapsed":462791},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980651640,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":2911,"timeElapsed":465703},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980654192,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":2550,"timeElapsed":468255},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980667168,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":11199,"timeElapsed":481231},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980669024,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":1854,"timeElapsed":483087},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980670520,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":1495,"timeElapsed":484583},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980672864,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":2343,"timeElapsed":486927},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980674575,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":1710,"timeElapsed":488638},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980676368,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":1792,"timeElapsed":490431},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980678976,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":2606,"timeElapsed":493039},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980680759,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":1783,"timeElapsed":494822},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980682439,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"36","question":"Describe a time you felt most full of joy.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":1679,"timeElapsed":496502},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980701831,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":17799,"timeElapsed":515894},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980704887,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":3055,"timeElapsed":518950},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980706799,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":1911,"timeElapsed":520862},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980709095,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":2295,"timeElapsed":523158},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980711559,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":2463,"timeElapsed":525622},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980713431,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":1871,"timeElapsed":527494},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980718839,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":5407,"timeElapsed":532902},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980721639,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":2799,"timeElapsed":535702},{"subjectID":"aa7y9ae876","prolificID":"673339f9cd44380670e5a700","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b235a13eb33a1577c697","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980724511,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":2871,"timeElapsed":538574}]